

### Apprentice UI/UX designer

BRADLEY M. HILL

#### **ABOUT**

After gaining my degree in Philosophy from the University of Hull I traveled to the colds of Canada and the heats of Australia, learning the arts of cuisinary delight and building further upon my Bar management experience, I have since been cheffing and baking and now look to break into the weird and wonderful world of UI/UX Design.

#### CONTACT

07707 214 161

brad.michael.hill@gmail.com

www.bradleyawesome.com

71 Sherborne Road, Yeovil, BA21 4HE

#### **EXPERTISE**

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**



#### Walled Garden Restaurant

2019 - Present

#### Chef de Partie

Working here has allowed me to work closely with the Head Chef designing various seasonal dishes that have featured on our menu.

- · Time management and lots of short deadlines.
- Creativity with flavour combinations, plating and garnishing.
- Clear and concise communication as we synchronise our orders and timings.



## Grand Parc de Puy du Fou 2017 - 2019

#### Kitchen Manager

Very high traffic kitchen where our front and back of house teams had to work together to satisfy the demand.

- Leadership was tested with the different teams I worked with each year.
- My fluency and confidence in my French continued to increase and be refined.
- Managing the daily scheduling to best manage the flow of customers in the Parc.

#### **EDUCATION**



# Google Foundations of UX Design 2022- Present



# University of Bath Spa 2022

#### **Bootcamp in Creative Computing**

 Introduction to the fundamentals of UI/UX design, as well as showing us how different techniques and approaches impact the final design.



### University of Hull

2006 - 2009

#### **BA Philosophy**

 Critical thinking, problem solving, Logic and reason, along with Abstract ideas being examined analysed and tested. Creative thinking and strong communication skills.